Guide to the Yale Divinity School STM Theses
Yale University Divinity School Library
- S.T.M. Theses on Microfiche, Series IV
  - Lara, James R.: Bipolar liturgical space in medieval Spain: the Coro Baio and Via Sacra, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0052
  - Lee, Hwain: Confucius, Christ and co-partnership: competing liturgies for the soul of Korean American women, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0053
  - Liles, Linda Kathleen: Guide to the pilgrim churches at Rome: a late 15th century manuscript in Yale University's Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0054
  - Mlay, Joel J.: Pharisees in the second temple period: Pietists or legalists?, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0056
  - Person, Gretchen E.: Expression of joy, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0057
  - Sheely, Steve (Stephen R.): Intimacy in the early church and pagan groups, 1990
    See Fiche B3500 0059
  - Beams, Ann Muenzer: The Bible: a user's guide, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0061
  - Cho, Dong-Ho: Mode of production in premonarchic Israel, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0062
  - Ellis, Jim: Echoes behind the mask: a yearning for intimacy in ministry, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0063
  - Engelbrecht, Olaf: Function of the churches in the legitimation of proslavery arguments in the south, 1619-1800, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0064
  - Holleman, Joost: Resurrection and the eschatological hero: an inquiry into the relationship between the resurrection and the eschatological hero, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0065
  - Kwon, Kyeong-Seog: Correlation of ontology and the doctrine of God: in the philosophical theology of Paul Tillich, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0066
  - O'Connor, Patrick H.: Family therapy of substance abuse: implications for the Caribbean church, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0067
  - Pillay, Hendrick: Black theology and black consciousness: towards developing a black theological hermeneutic for South Africa, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0068
  - Snyder, Greg: Altum est: a study of the sacraments in the Gospel of Philip, 1991
    See Fiche B3500 0075
  - Cho, Young Hwan: Religious conscientization and political socialization in modernizing Korean society, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0069
  - Kim, Younglae: Imagination and religious education in the electronic media age, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0074
  - Lord, Richard A.: Liturgical evangelism: forming Christian faith through worship, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0070
  - Sopo'Aga, Ekitoa M.: Jesus Christ as captive and liberator of culture in Samoa, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0073
  - Wilcots, Anthony W.: Who is responsible? an exploration of the black church's charge to bring wholeness to the suffering African American family, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0071
  - Yun, Koo D.: Pneumatology of Karl Barth and Wolfhart Pannenberg, 1992
    See Fiche B3500 0072
  - Boline, James E.: Disciple whom Jesus loves: a theology of lesbian and gay ritual practice, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0088
  - Bush, Michael D.: But is it natural theology? Emil Brunner and the reformed doctrine of the knowledge of God, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0093
  - Eschen-Pipes, L. Kathleen: Campus ministry and sexuality, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0091
  - Keucher, Gerald W. Rule of formation in the early church: the disciplina arcani re-examined, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0087
  - Patton, Paul: Secundum usum sarum: the sarum rite then and now, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0092
  - Ruff, Anthony: Choir in historical perspective, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0090
  - Silishebo, Silishebo: African proverbs and pastoral counseling in a Zambia perspective, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0094
  - Spaulding, Beth: Literature for the transition: the book of the worship of the United Church of Christ, 1994
    See Fiche B3500 0089
  - Graham, Preston Don: True Presbyterian: a case study of border state dissent during the American Civil War, 1995
    Fiche B3500 0095
  - Kucera, Patrick James Zachary: Themes on the cross and redemption: sermons based on liturgical year "B", 1995
    Fiche B3500 0096
  - Schroeder, Jeffery C.: Opening pleasantries in second John: an integrative historical analysis, 1995
    See Fiche B3500 0097